incfile.com 2018-08-12

# IncFile.com LLCC Privacy Policy

## We at IncFile.com, LLC have designed our business practices to safeguard your privacy.

This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or to people we do not employ. Therefore, we are not responsible forthe privacy practices or the content of such other businesses.

You can visit IncFile.com, LLC without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself. By using this site, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy.

### Collection of Data

There will be times, such as when you communicate with us by e-mail, submit an application, request a quote, purchase a product, etc., when we will need to obtain personally identifiable information from you or about you. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, social security number, financial information, credit references, etc. The information we receive about you or from you may be used by us or shared (including evaluating and obtaining financial products or services) by us with our corporate affiliates, agents, vendors and other third parties to help process your request or complete a transaction; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our customers’ needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services (of us or our business associates) in which you may be interested. We may also combine information you provide us with information about you that is available to us internally or from other sources. We believe that knowing more about you can enable us to serve you better.

You should be aware that we do not collect usage information about you when you visit our site, and we do not use “cookies.”

We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications on our website or other forms
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others
  * Information about you we may receive from credit reporting agencies.

### Personal Data Protection

We safeguard your personal data (e.g., credit card and finance application information) during electronic transmission from you to us using known encryption, security standards and procedures. We restrict access to non-public personal information about you only to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and other procedural safeguards to comply with applicable privacy laws to guard your nonpublic personal information. We also assess new technology for protecting sensitive customer information on an ongoing basis. However, if your information is forwarded to a dealership or other third party provider, your information will be transmitted according to the security and privacy policies of that dealership or third party provider whose privacy practices may differ from ours. Your information as shared with outside providers will become subject to those different privacy policies.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. The only personal information a cookie can obtain is information supplied by the user. A cookie cannot read data from your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your web browser and you do not need to have cookies turned on to successfully use our website. Most browsers are defaulted to accept and maintain cookies and you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or not.

IncFile uses a cookie to identify return user visits to our website. This information is used to understand the differences in use between a new user and a returning user.

We do not store any personal information about you within these cookies.

### Third Party Advertising

We do not use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website.

### Trademark and Copyright Information

Everything on our website is copyrighted (unless otherwise noted) and may not be used except with our express written consent. Use of these images by you or other third parties is prohibited and may violate the copyright laws, trademark laws, privacy laws and other laws and regulations. Nothing contained on this site may be construed as granting any license or right to use any of our trademarks or service marks without our prior written consent. 

### Privacy Policy Questions

Please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy at our website, so be sure to check back here frequently.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or privacy policies, please feel free to e-mail your questions to us at [incfile-info@incfile.com](mailto:incfile-info@incfile.com)

### Opt Out Policy

IncFile may send promotional emails, newsletters, notices and other forms of communication ("Messages") to users and/or customers who have opted in to receive such messages. Generally, our users and customers may not opt-out of service-related or transactional communications, as those are not promotional but pertain to your business relationship with IncFile. However, if you do not wish to receive promotional Messages you can opt-out by using the "Unsubscribe" link and following the associated instructions or by emailing us at [support@incfile.com.](mailto:support@incfile.com)
